You may now kick the bride.
Revenge of the Bridesmaids is a comedy, romance, tv
movie film directed by James Hayman.
Two women plot revenge against the woman marrying their friend's ex-boyfriend.
Abigail, played by Raven-Symoné.
Parker, played by JoAnna Garcia Swisher.
Olivia, played by Beth Broderick.
Rachel, played by Chryssie Whitehead.
Caitlyn, played by Virginia Williams.
Ashley, played by Lacey Minchew.
Revenge of the Bridesmaids is a 2010 ABC Family Original
Movie that premiered on July 18, 2010.
It stars Raven-Symoné as Abigail and JoAnna García as Parker,
undercover bridesmaids with a mission to break up a wedding.
In addition, the film's cast also features Virginia Williams, Beth Broderick, Chryssie
Whitehead, David Clayton Rogers, Lyle Brocato and Brittany Ishibashi.
The film explores themes of undercover, bridesmaid,
female friendship, wedding, sabotage.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.